Our educational system is in huge crisis.
我们的教育系统正处于巨大的危机之中。
What troubles me is that
令我烦恼的是，
the way we're defining that crisis is
我们对这一危机的定义是，
it's a fiscal crisis or it's a structural crisis
它是一个财政危机，或者是一个结构性危机，
or it's a crisis of kids who can't pass tests.
或者是一个无法通过考试的孩子的危机。
We're not defining it the way I think we need to define it
我们没有按照我认为我们需要的方式来定义它，
which is a crisis in our failure to support the people
即我们未能支持那些在生活的
doing the work at the deepest levels of their lives.
最深处从事工作的人的危机。
Teaching is very demanding work,
教学是一项要求非常高的工作，
teaching requires a heart as well as a mind.
教学需要用脑，也需要用心。
Teaching requires a capacity to create
教学需要一种能力，
hospitable space for young people
为那些害怕、
who are fearful, who are anxious about life
对生活和被要求学习的东西感到焦虑的年轻人
and about what they're being asked to learn.
创造一个好客的空间。
And if we can't support the people
如果我们不能通过
who are doing that demanding work
向他们提供热情好客，
by extending to them hospitality,
向他们提供有助于
by extending to them the things that help
扩大和深化
enlarge and deepen their hearts,
他们的心灵的东西，
as well as the information
以及他们所需要的教学信息和教学技巧，
they need to teach and the techniques they need to teach,
来支持那些正在从事这项艰巨工作的人，
then I think we've got a real crisis on our hands
那么我认为我们就会有一个真正的危机，
and indeed we do.
事实上我们就有此危机。